Inventory of the Ultimate weapon: the H-bomb dilemma video tape
Hoover Institution Archives
- 1988
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor #98, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Shapiro/Kaupas (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary Operation Ivy Operation Greenhouse, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, 1 HR Drop-Frame TC on Ch.2, Ivy :36, Greenhouse :25 (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #91, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #92, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #93, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 18)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #94, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 17)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #95, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 18)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #96, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 30)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #97, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 27)
  - "Superbomb" Ted and Caro Taylor Reel #98, 14 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 27)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor Reel 93, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Cam/Sound: Shapiro/Kaupos (Box 26)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor Reel 95, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Cam/Sound: Shapiro/Kaupos (Box 24)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor Reel 92 "Superbomb", 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1= Peter and Pam, Ch2= Theodore and Caro Taylor (Box 28)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor Reel 93 "Superbomb", 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Cam/Sound=Shapiro/Kaupas (Box 28)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor Reel 96, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Cam=Shapiro, Sound=Kaupas (Box 26)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor Reel 97, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam (Box 26)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor "Superbomb" Reel #91, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam (Box 28)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor "Superbomb" Reel #91, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1- Peter and Pam, Ch2- Theodore and Caro Taylor (Box 2)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor "Superbomb" Reel #92, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam (Box 1)
  - Ted and Caro Taylor "Superbomb" Reel #94, 14 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1- Peter and Pam, Ch2- Theodore and Caro Taylor (Box 24)
  - "Superbomb" Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #107, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1-Interviewer, Ch2- Victor Weisskopt (Box 24)
  - #105 Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam (Box 21)
  - Smith Hoving #102, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1-Interviewer, Ch2-Smith (Box 22)
  - Smith Hoving #103, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam (Box 23)
  - Smith Hoving #103, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1-Interviewer, Ch2. Smith, TC 00:22:00 UB 102 (Box 24)
  - Smith Hoving #99, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam (Box 24)
  - Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #100, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1-Interviewer, Ch2- Smith (Box 24)
  - Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #101, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1-Interviewer, Ch2- Smith (Box 23)
  - Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #99, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1-Interviewer, Ch2- Smith (Box 28)
  - "Superbomb" Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary Reel #100, 16 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 2)
  - "Superbomb" Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary Reel #101, 16 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 28)
  - "Superbomb" Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary Reel #99, 16 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 22)
  - "Superbomb" Smith Hoving Reel #102, 16 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 3)
  - "Superbomb" Smith Hoving Reel #103, 16 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 22)
  - "Superbomb" Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary Reel #104, 16 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 12/21/88 (Box 2)
  - Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #104, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam (Box 23)
  - Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #106, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1-Interviewer, Ch2- Weisskopt (Box 27)
  - Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #104, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1- Interviewer, Ch2- Weisskopf (Box 24)
  - Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary #105, 16 Dec 1988; Betacam, Ch1- Interviewer, Ch2- Weisskopf (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary Reel #105, 21 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 10)
  - "Superbomb" Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary Reel #106, 21 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Victor Weisskopf, Smith Hoving, Greg McCleary Reel #107, 21 Dec 1988; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 12)
- 1989
  - "Superbomb" #110 Interview With Ambassador Paul Nitze (cont.), 27 Jan 1989; Betacam, Ch1-Nitze, Ch2-Pam (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Gordon Arnison Tape #113, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam, Interview with Gordon Arnison (cont.) Room Tone at End (Box 10)
  - "Superbomb" Paul Nitze Interview Tape #108, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam, Camera: Tom Kaufman, Audio: Bob Silverthorne (Ch1-Nitze, Ch2-Pam) (Box 11)
  - "Superbomb" Paul Nitze Tape #109, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam, Interview with Ambassador Paul Nitze (cont.) Ch1=Nitze, Ch2=Pam (Box 12)
  - "Superbomb" Tape #114 Stills of Ted Taylor, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam, Arneson Interview, Stills with room tone (Box 12)
  - #111 "Superbomb" Gordon Arnison, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam, Interview with Gordon Arnison (Channel 1= Arnison, Channel 2=Pam) (Box 12)
  - #112 "Superbomb" Gordon Arnison, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam, Interview with Gordon Arnison (Channel 1= Arnison, Channel 2=Pam) (Box 11)
  - Interview with Gordon Arnison Tape #111, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam (Box 10)
  - Interview with Gordon Arnison Tape #112 (cont.), 27 Jan 1989; Betacam (Box 10)
  - Paul Nitze "Superbomb" #108, 27 Jan 1989; Betacam (Box 10)
  - "Superbomb" Int. With Ambassador Paul Nitze Tape #108, 27 Jan 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 2/2/89 (Box 10)
  - "Superbomb" Int. With Ambassador Paul Nitze Tape #109, 27 Jan 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 2/2/89 (Box 9)
  - "Superbomb" Int. With Ambassador Paul Nitze Tape #110, 27 Jan 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 2/2/89 (Box 9)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Gordon Arnison Tape #111, 27 Jan 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 2/2/89 (Box 9)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Gordon Arnison Tape #112, 27 Jan 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 2/2/89 (Box 9)
  - "Superbomb" Interview With Gordon Arnison Tape #113, 27 Jan 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code 2/2/89 (Box 9)
  - "Superbomb" Stills of Ted and Caro Taylor Room Tone- Arnison Int. Tape #114, 2 Feb 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 9)
  - "Superbomb" Lt. Col. Robert Johnson Interview #115, 20 Feb 1989; Betacam, Poway, CA, Camera: Peter Pilafia, 2/20, Dolby/Non Drop Frame (Box 14)
  - "Superbomb" Lt. Col. Robert Johnson Interview #116, 20 Feb 1989; Betacam, 2/20, Dolby/Non-Drop (Box 13)
  - "Superbomb" Lt. Col. Robert Johnson 2/20 Tape #115, 28 Feb 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 9)
  - "Superbomb" Lt. Col. Robert Johnson 2/20 Tape #116, 28 Feb 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 8)
  - "Superbomb" Lt. Col. Robert Johnson 2/20 Tape #117, 28 Feb 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code (Box 8)
  - Movietone, 7 Aug 1989; U-Matic (1) "Pres has made a crucial decision," (2) Svaun River Plant (3) Birth of New H Bomb Plant (4) Does Russia Possess the H Bomb? (5) Civilization at the Crossroads (6) "Atomic Race or World Control?" (7) Deal or H Bomb Test (Box 8)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #10, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code, Truman: Congress (Communist Treat-Greece Turkey, Truman: Congress (The Draft- Military Readiness), Truman: Dinner Event-Anti Wallace, Berlin Airlift Reds Converse on Chinese Capital, A-Bomb-Security After Joe 1 (Box 9)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #10, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer (Box 9)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #11, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code, Cold War Builds, Korea, Truman Short Speech, Truman Cadillac Square, Achesan (Box 9)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #11, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer (Box 10)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #12, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code, Turman Speech, UN Pickets (MOS Inside) (Box 10)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #12, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer (Box 10)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #13, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code, Korea, Speech, Bernard Baruch in General Assembly (Box 8)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #13, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer (Box 6)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #14, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 8)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #14, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam (Box 4)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #14, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer, 213 (Box 3)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #15, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 4)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #15, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam (Box 3)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #15, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer, 211 (Box 3)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #16, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 3)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #16, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer, 212 (Box 2)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #16, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam (Box 16)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #17, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub With Visual Time Code, Airwar Against Japan, A-Bomb Explosions, Card Computers, Oppi and Dean (MOS) (Box 6)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #17, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam (Box 6)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #17, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer, 214 (Box 27)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #18, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 27)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #18, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Tranfer (Box 24)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #19, 9 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 6)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #19, 9 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer (Box 6)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #20, 23 Oct 1989; U-Matic, Film Transfer Dub with Visual Time Code (Box 6)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape #20, 23 Oct 1989; Betacam (Box 15)
  - Pam Hogan "Big Bombs" Tape 20, 23 Oct 1989; Betacam, Film Transfer Dub, 215 (Box 15)
  - Super Bomb Documentary: W.R. Smith Flat Art Animation, 1 Nov 1989; U-Matic (Box 15)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary, 1 Nov 1989; Betacam, W.R. Smith Flat Art Animation, 516 (Box 15)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary W.R. Smith Flart Art Animation, 1 Nov 1989; Betacam (Box 24)
  - Super Bomb Documentary 2-89644, 2 Nov 1989; U Matic, "Baruch's Plan," "World Weighs Impact," "Russia and the Atom," "Truman Denounces Soviets," "World Faces Gravest Crisis/War" (Box 28)
  - Pam Hogan Super Bomb Documentary, 5 Dec 1989; U-Matic, W.R. Smith Flat Art Animation TCBI (Box 28)
- 1990-1991
  - #1 Garwin, 17 Dec 1990; Betacam (Box 29)
  - #2 Garwin, 17 Dec 1990; Betacam (Box 13)
  - #3 Garwin, 17 Dec 1990; Betacam (Box 13)
  - #4 Garwin, 17 Dec 1990; Betacam (Box 13)
  - "Superbomb" Barton Bernstein, Interview at Stanford University, #200, 25 May 1991; Betacam, 25.5.9 (Box 14)
  - "Superbomb" Barton Bernstein at Stanford University #202, 25 May 1991; Betacam, 25.5.91, Aud, 1 and 2 Looped Boom (Box 14)
  - "Superbomb" Barton Bernstein at Stanford University #203, 25 May 1991; Betacam, 25.5.91 (cont.) AVD-1 and 2 Looped Boom (Box 14)
  - "Superbomb" Barton Berstein at Stanford University #201, 25 May 1991; Betacam, 25.5.91 (cont.) AVD-1 and 2 Looped Boom (Box 29)
  - "Superbomb" Edward Teller, 25 May 1991; Betacam (Cont.) Interview, #205, 26.5.97 (Box 31)
  - "Superbomb" Edward Teller #204, 26 May 1991; Betacam, 26.5.91 (Box 14)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #1 Interview with Richard Garwin, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 12)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #2 Interview with Richard Garwin, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 12)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #200 Interview With Barton Bernstein, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 25)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #201 Interview With Barton Bernstein, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 5)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #202 Interview With Barton Bernstein, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 5)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #203 Interview With Barton Bernstein, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 5)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #204 Interview With Edward Teller, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 5)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #205 Interview With Edward Teller, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 4)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #3 Interview with Richard Garwin, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 4)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Tape #4 Interview with Richard Garwin, 24 Jun 1991; U-Matic, With Visual Time Code (Box 4)
- 1997-1998
  - Interview With Vasily Ginzberg Tape #1 Princeton, NJ, 25 Apr 1997; Betacam, Ch1= Program Sound, Ch2= Question Sound, Camera Dick Blofson, Sound Scott Nielson (Box 5)
  - Interview With Vasily Ginzberg Tape #2 Princeton, NJ, 25 Apr 1997; Betacam, Ch1=Program Sound, Ch2=Question Sound (Box 32)
  - Interview With Vasily Ginzberg Tape #3 Princeton, NJ, 25 Apr 1997; Betacam, Ch1=Program Sound, Ch2=Question Sound (Box 32)
  - Barton Berstein "Superbomb" (cont.) #199, 25 May 1997; Betacam (Box 28)
  - "Superbomb" Barton Bernstein Stanford University, 25 May 1997; Betacam (Box 28)
  - "Superbomb" Hans Bethe #2, 11 Dec 1998; Betacam (Box 31)
  - "Superbomb" Hans Bethe #3, 11 Dec 1998; Betacam (Box 5)
- 2000
  - The Great H-Bomb Debate Short Version, 5 Jan 2000; VHS, Pam Hogan Length 43:25 (Box 13)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary Inc. NARA 208, 17 Jan 2000; Betacam, 1) VJ Day, 2) VJ Day, 3) AEC Exterior (Box 13)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary Co. Archives Dub R#111 SM 74 Part 1, 18 Jan 2000; Betacam, TRT 10:00, 204 (Box 13)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary, 19 Jan 2000; Betacam (Box 14)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary, 25 Jan 2000; Betacam, NARA Stock Footage #001249, CR#: 342 USAF 14365 R1 and R2 (Box 14)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary NARA Stock Footage #001249, 25 Jan 2000; Betacam SP, 201, DF Timecode Starts @ 1 HR, One Light Transfer (Box 15)
  - Tape #1 The Ultimate Weapon, 16 Feb 2000; Betacam (Box 15)
  - Tape #2 The Ultimate Weapon, 17 Feb 2000; Betacam, 302 (Box 15)
  - Tape #3 The Ultimate Weapon, 22 Feb 2000; Betacam (Box 15)
  - Tape #4 The Ultimate Weapon, 22 Feb 2000; Betacam, 304 (Box 15)
  - The Ultimate Weapon, 1 Mar 2000; Betacam, 305 (Box 15)
- Includes historic footage, undated
  - #118 "Superbomb" P. Galison 2, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild 6172544695 (Box 14)
  - #12 John Wheeler/Princeton, undated; Betacam (Box 13)
  - #2, undated; Betacam (Box 13)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" #117, #118, undated; U-Matic, With BITC and ATTC (Box 3)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" #118, #120, undated; U-Matic, With BITC and ATTC (Box 3)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" Erikson 126, undated; Betacam, Chalkboard Hallway to Door (Box 3)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" P. Galison 1, undated; Betacam, CR 117, 254-4695 (Box 22)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" P. Galison 5, undated; Betacam, CR 121, 254-4695 (Box 22)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" Sherwin #4, undated; Betacam, CR 125 (Box 22)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" Sherwin #1, #2, undated; U-Matic, CR 122 and 123, With ATTC With Visible Time Code (Box 23)
  - Documentary Guild "Superbomb" Sherwin #3, #4, undated; U-Matic, CR 124 and 125, With ATTC and Visible Time Code (Box 1)
  - Edit Decision List "The Ulitmate Weapon" GVG 7.0 Sort Mode E, undated; 3 1/2 inch floppy disk (Box 25)
  - EDL Test for "The Ultimate Weapon" V1 Only GVG7, undated; 3 1/2 inch floppy disk (Box 26)
  - Dasiac #2, undated; Betacam (Box 13)
  - Dasiac Footage Vol. 7 Shot off Steenbeck, undated; U-Matic, Ivy? Shots inside Mike (Box 26)
  - Dasiac Footage-H Bomb Vol. 3, undated; U-Matic, Operation Greenhouse 9 May 51- 27 June 51 (10 Minutes) (Box 32)
  - Dasiac Footage-Ivy Vol. 1, undated; U-Matic, Dasiac Footage-Greenhouse Series, 6 July 50-15 December 50 (Box 32)
  - Dasiac Footage-Ivy Vol. 5, undated; U-Matic, Dasiac Footage Volume 5, Ivy, 25 September 52-12 October 52 (Box 32)
  - Dasiac Footage-Ivy Vol. 6, undated; U-Matic, Dasiac Footage Volume 6 shot from Stecubeck-Ivy, 14 October 52-1 November 52 (Box 25)
  - Dasiac Footbage Vol. 2 Shott off Steenbeck Operation Greenhouse, undated; U-Matic, 11 Jan 51- 6 May 51 (Box 3)
  - Dasiac Footbage-Ivy Vol. 4, undated; U-Matic, Dasiac Footage-Ivy Volume 4, 9 June 52- 25 September 52 (Box 3)
  - History Undercover 222, undated; VHS (Box 30)
  - Los Alamos National Lab History 1943-1945, undated; U-Matic (Box 30)
  - New Atlantic Library Miscellany, undated; U-Matic, D-Day Celebrations Times Square, Roosevelt, 1948 Elections, Berlin Aircraft, Stalin, Korea, Crowd Scenes, Stills, Portland Oregon Civil Defense Drill (Box 29)
  - New Atlantic Miscellany, undated; U-Matic, Pathe 4: Berlin After War/Bombed Berlin, Misc Bomb Explosions, Aair Force Film Footage, Truman-Talks About Bombing Japan, Pathe 3: Czech Coup//Pathe 16: China// Pathe 17: China, Truman Man from Missouri Selects, Pathe 18: Truman Inauguration (Box 26)
  - Operation Ivy: Sync Selects, undated; U-Matic, R.306 (1) Intro George Test (cut section from Greenhouse) (Box 26)
  - Operation Ivy U.S. Air Force, undated; U-Matic, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Pathe Newsreels #6 Cold War, undated; U-Matic (2) Picket Line Re Hungary (3) Dean G. Acheson Succeeds Marshall (4) UN_Soviets Reject Baruch (5) Berlin BG (6) Churchill Re Berlin (Addresses British Crowd (7) Eagle and the Bear: 1945: Los Alamos (8) Red Army Images-Pathe #11 (Box 28)
  - Pathe Newsreels R.13 New Atlantic, undated; U-Matic (1) Hiroshima Aftermath (2) Cyclotron in England (3) 5th Warning: Hiroshima Victims/ Bikini Test (4) Britain's H Bomb (5) Truman on Baruch Plan (6) "The Mighty Atom," (7) Atomic Bomb-The Big Test (8) H Bomb/ US Scientists Go Ahead (9) US Reveals Atomic Work (10) Atlee Visits US Speaks About Atomic Bomb (Box 29)
  - "Superbomb" 127, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild GAC #1 (Box 5)
  - "Superbomb" 128, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild Window (Box 14)
  - "Superbomb" CR 119 P. Galison 3, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild 2544695 (Box 8)
  - "Superbomb" CR 122 Sherwin #1, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild (Box 7)
  - "Superbomb" CR 123 Sherwin #2, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild (Box 26)
  - "Superbomb" CR 124 Sherwin #3, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild (Box 21)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Bomb" #24, undated; Betacam, Length 3:45 (Box 24)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super", undated; U-Matic, Dasiac #4 (Box 2)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super", undated; Betacam, Length 19:45 (Box 22)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super", undated; Betacam, Length 19:45 (Box 26)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super" Reels 1/2, undated; U-Matic, Tape #1 (Box 16)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super" Reels 2 and 3 Tape #2, undated; Betacam, Length 17:56 (Box 7)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super" Reels 2/3, undated; U-Matic, Tape #2, Dasiac #2 (Box 7)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super" Tape #1 Reels 1 and 2, undated; Betacam, Length 30 min. (Box 7)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary "The Super" Tape #1 Reels 1 and 2, undated; Betacam, DASIAC Reel 1 59:15:07 (Box 8)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary Inc. "The Ultimate Weapon", undated; Betacam SP, Digital Cut From Avid, 212 579 0503 (Box 8)
  - "Superbomb" Documentary, Operation Ivy Operation Greenhouse, undated; U-Matic, 1 HR Drop-Frame TC on Ch.2, Ivy :36, Greenhouse :25 (Box 7)
  - "Superbomb" P. Galison R 130, undated; Betacam (Box 8)
  - The Air Force Story, undated; U-Matic, B/W 16mm Film SFP-263-Vol 2-1, Dub From New Atlantic 3/4 Copie Via ABC (Box 8)
  - The Documentary Guild "Superbomb" #121, undated; U-Matic, with BITC and ATTC (Box 7)
  - The Documentary Guild "Superbomb" P. Galison, undated; U-Matic, With ATTC and Visible Time Code (Box 7)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary "The Bomb", undated; U-Matic, Dasiac #3, UBIT #24 (Box 22)
  - The "Superbomb" Documentary "The Bomb", undated; Betacam, Length 3:45, UBIT #24 (Box 25)
  - "Superbomb" Lt. Col. Robert Johnson Interview #117, undated; Betacam, 2/20, Dolby/Non-Drop (Box 26)
  - "Superbomb" CR 120 P. Galison 4, undated; Betacam, Documentary Guild 254-4695 (Box 29)
  - The Documentary Guild "Superbomb" GAC, undated; U-Matic, With ATTC and Visible Time Code (Box 29)